Deepakshi Ralia

Software Developer in Test

Experienced SDET (Manual & Automation) engineer with 2.3 years in the industry in various domains such as Banking, Gaming, etc., leading test operations in teams of varying sizes in designing and conducting complex test cases & scenarios.

deepakshiraliya12345@gmail.com

+918872282176

ludhiana, India

207

in.linkedin.com/in/deepakshi-ralia-59085b207

github.com/Akshi1808 🧲

WORK EXPERIENCE

LIGHT & WONDER / (Manual + Automation) PureSoftware Pvt Ltd

01/2022 - Present

Noida

Achievements/Tasks

- Python automation project involves the automation of application named 'Casino MarketPlace'.
- It aims to automate the interaction with the CMP app, reducing manual Intervention and increasing accuracy in processing Transactions.
- Worked on these technologies Python, SG Mutate (FrameWork),
 PyWinAuto, MySQL, Azure Data Studio

Manual + Automation / Web Automation PureSoftware Pvt Ltd

01/2022 - Present

Noida

Achievements/Tasks

- Used JIRA, Postman, Jenkins, Putty, MySQL for manual Automation.
- Used Selenium for web automation by running all of web application's tests. When working on this project, gained skills in TestNG which is a testing framework that makes Selenium tests easier to understand.

Arttha (Manual Testing) PureSoftware Pvt Ltd

01/2022 - Present

Noida

Achievements/Tasks

 Working in an Agile (SCRUM) environment/team focusing on sprint by sprint deliveries Experience with relational databases, DBeaver and Microsoft SQL Server data manipulation. Experience with JIRA Software for Test Planning. Active interest in web application development. Interest in product testing. Ability to derive test scenarios from user stories and use cases.

EDUCATION

Graduation

B.tech (Computer Science & Engineering)

07/2018 - 06/2022 82.3%

Post Matriculation

Dasmesh Sen Sec School

04/2016 - 04/2017 87.1%

Matriculation

New SMD Sen Sec School

04/2013 - 04/2014 84.4%

SKILLS



ACHIEVEMENTS

Lead a team of five within a broader team of 33 members, concurrently managing responsibilities on both the client and team sides, effectively mitigating and resolving challenges to streamline operations and enhance overall efficiency. (05/2023 - Present)

CERTIFICATES

Certificate of completion of Latex training (06/2020 - 07/2020)

from spoken tutorial IIT Bombay

Certificate of completion of Python 3.4.3 training (06/2020 - 07/2020)

from spoken tutorial IIT Bombay

Certification of completion of Java (12/2021 - 03/2022)

from Udemy

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Hind

Full Professional Proficiency

Punjabi

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Reading | Cricket

Music

Learning

Deepakshi Ralia

Software Engineer

Experienced software engineer with 2.4 years in the industry in various domains such as Banking, Gaming, etc., leading test operations in teams of varying sizes in designing and conducting complex test cases, scripting & scenarios.

deepakshiraliya12345@gmail.com

+918872282176

ludhiana, India

in.linkedin.com/in/deepakshi-ralia-59085b207

github.com/Akshi1808 📮

WORK EXPERIENCE

LIGHT & WONDER

PureSoftware Pvt Ltd

01/2022 - Present

Noida

Achievements/Tasks

- Python automation project involves the automation of application named 'Casino MarketPlace'.
- It aims to automate the interaction with the CMP app, reducing manual Intervention and increasing accuracy in processing Transactions.
- Worked on these technologies Python, SG Mutate (FrameWork),
 PyWinAuto, MySQL, Azure Data Studio

Web Automation

PureSoftware Pvt Ltd
01/2022 - Present

Noida

Achievements/Tasks

- Used JIRA, Postman, Jenkins, Putty, MySQL for manual Automation.
- Used Selenium for web automation by running all of web application's tests. When working on this project, gained skills in TestNG which is a testing framework that makes Selenium tests easier to understand.

Arttha

PureSoftware Pvt Ltd

01/2022 - Present

Noida

Achievements/Tasks

 Working in an Agile (SCRUM) environment/team focusing on sprint by sprint deliveries Experience with relational databases, DBeaver and Microsoft SQL Server data manipulation. Experience with JIRA Software for Test Planning. Active interest in web application development. Interest in product testing. Ability to derive test scenarios from user stories and use cases.

EDUCATION

Graduation

B.tech (Computer Science & Engineering)

07/2018 - 06/2022 82.3%

Post Matriculation

Dasmesh Sen Sec School

04/2016 - 04/2017 87.1%

Matriculation

New SMD Sen Sec School

04/2013 - 04/2014 84.4%

SKILLS



ACHIEVEMENTS

Lead a team of five within a broader team of 33 members, concurrently managing responsibilities on both the client and team sides, effectively mitigating and resolving challenges to streamline operations and enhance overall efficiency. (05/2023 - Present)

CERTIFICATES

Certificate of completion of Latex training (06/2020 - 07/2020)

from spoken tutorial IIT Bombay

Certificate of completion of Python 3.4.3 training (06/2020 - 07/2020)

from spoken tutorial IIT Bombay

Certification of completion of Java (12/2021 - 03/2022)

from Udemy

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Hindi

Full Professional Proficiency

Puniab

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Reading Cricket

Music

Learning